[Music]
submitting claims online is the fastest
easiest way to get your benefits
processed in this video i'll show you
how to submit a claim online
start by logging on to the plan member
site and selecting submit a claim
click continue to go to the submit a
claim page
choose the plan that you want your claim
paid from
from the drop down menu choose the type
of service you're claiming is it for
dental
health
paramedical or other
next choose the person the claim is for
is it for yourself or a family member
if you have additional coverage
available for example through your
spouse's plan be sure to include that
information so we can coordinate
coverage and get you the maximum payment
back
now we need to know who provided the
service
if they're already in our system select
their name from the list
if it's a new service provider enter
their information into the system
and click continue
next enter the expense information for
your claim
the details required will vary depending
on the type of service provided
now save the expense submission and
attach any receipts or other required
documents
before submitting your claim check that
your banking and contact information are
correct
direct deposit is the fastest way to get
your money back and it's easy to set up
finally read through the terms and
conditions check the consent box and
submit your claim the confirmation page
lets you know that your claim has been
successfully submitted make a note of
the confirmation number for reference
you can also find a record of your claim
by clicking recent claims from your home
page
savini claims online is fast and easy
and when you download the manulife
mobile app you can submit claims anytime
anywhere
these are just some of the ways manulife
makes managing your benefits easy and
secure